Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty; Records apap401
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Partnerships with Related Organizations, 1976-2022
  - Witness to Innocence
    - Diocese of Covington Employee/Volunteer Information Document for Mike VonAllmen, 2020 February 17
    - Mike VonAllmen Photograph, 2020 February 24
    - VonAllmen Event poster "Death Penalty: Yes or No", 2020 March 18
    - Randy Steidl Events Graphic, Color Itinerary, 2012 November
    - Randy Steidl Events, Color Itinerary, 2012 November
    - Gary Drinkard Exoneree Tour, 2014 September
    - Exoneree Tour Featuring Kirk Bloodsworth Intinerary, 2014 November
    - Final Report Kirk Bloodsworth Tour, 2015 February
    - Final Report Kirk Bloodsworth Tour, Version 2, 2015 February
    - Budget for Kirk Bloodsworth Tour, 2015 February
    - KY Tour Questionaire Results, 2015 February
    - Kenbtucky Exoneree Tour, 2013 August 5-2013 August 18
    - Sabrina Butler's Schedule, 2014 March 12-2014 March 16
    - Death Row Exoneree Tour Dates, 2014 September-2014 October
    - Kirk Bloodsworth Schedule, 2014 November 10-2014 November 12
- Research and Subject Files, 2006-2015
  The Research and Subject Files series contains materials related to abolishing the death penalty in other states, marketing and organization guides (utilized by the Kentucky Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty but not written for them specifically), and other death penalty related reports.
  - Subject File, 1996; 1998 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Graphic of Quote from Abby Johnson, Pro-Life Advocate and Author, 2015 October 9
  - "30 Years After Gregg v. Georgia Grassroots Organizing Kit", 2006 May 21
  - Holy Spirit Bowling Green Names, 2008 September 13
  - DPIC Press Release "Connecticut Senate Near Crucial Vote on Bill to Repeal the Death Penalty: State Poised to Become Fifth Sttae in Five Years to Abolish Capital Punishment", 2012 April 3
  - DPIC "Death Penalty at a Glance: The Death Penalty in Decline", 2012 April 4
  - Texas Year-End Report "Damaging the Death Penalty Brand Through Year-End Reports", 2015 September 30
  - Texas Year-End Presentation "Damaging the Death Penalty Brand Through Year-End Reports", 2015 September 30
  - DPIC "The 2% Death Penalty: How a Minority of Counties Produce Most Death Cases At Enormous Costs to All" Report, 2013 October
  - "Increasing Engagement: How to Keep Members Active When Your Issues Aren't Hot" CQ Roll Call Report, 2015 June
  - Conneticuit Network to Abolish the Death Penalty Volunteer Brochure, 2011
- VHS Tapes, 1990-1998
  - "Legislative Research Commission Office of Public Information "Senate," Racial Justice Bill, 1998 February 5 (Box 3)
  - Kentucky Senate Bill 172, Mental Ineptitude, 1990 February 2 (Box 3)
  - Interview with Death Row Inmate Kevin Nigel Stanford (on death row since the age of 17) and Stephen Bright, Kentucky (Death Row Lawyer), Undated (Box 3)
  - Harold McQueen, Clemency Video, Undated (Box 3)
  - Legislative Research Commission, Office of Public Inforamtion "Senate", 1998 February 5 (Box 3)
  - Kentucky Racial Justice Act Legislative Debates, Copy, 1996 March 18; 1996 March 27 (Box 3)
  - Kentucky Racial Justice Act Legislative Debates, Original, 1996 March 18; 1996 March 27 (Box 3)
  - Legislative Research Commission, Office of Public Information, Senate, 1998 February 5 (Box 3)